Scott Caprisecca

caprisecca@gmail.com Portfolio LinkedIn

I'm an Email Developer specialized in working in a cross-functional environment to create responsive and high converting HTML emails. I have experience working with multiple email service providers for campaign deployment, while ensuring they follow CAN-SPAM requirements.

SKILLS & TOOLS

HTML/CSS JavaScript Git/GitHub Litmus/Email on Acid

Salesforce Marketing Cloud MailChimp Constant Contact Google My Business

Photoshop/Adobe XD Figma Hubspot WordPress

PROJECTS

The Aveson Bite

View Email - View Code

Email newsletter for a Charter School. They needed an email designed & a template built that they can reuse each month. I designed the email with Adobe XD, hand coded it with HTML/CSS and tested using Email on Acid.

Vineyard Email

View Email - View Code

This is an email newsletter template for a vineyard. It is fully responsive with fallbacks in place for older email clients that do not support modern features.

Greer Lodge Promotional Email

<u>View Email</u> - <u>View Code</u>

This is a promotional email for a Lodge in Greer, AZ. It highlights room deals with links to book the room. The email was hand coded with HTML/CSS and tested with Litmus.

Organifi Transactional Email

View Email - View Code

This is an order confirmation email built using Foundations for Email. This is a personal project I completed to get experience using the Foundation framework.

Bookmark Extension Landing Page

View Site - View Code

This is a landing page design built using HTML, CSS and vanilla JavaScript. The design is from a frontend mentor challenge that I built using a PNG image.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer — Email Developer

June 2020 - Present

- Work directly with clients to gather requirements and convert these into error-free email code.
- Worked with Email Service Providers including MailChimp, Constant Contact and Salesforce Marketing Cloud.
- Experienced with building HTML emails from designs created in Photoshop, Figma and Adobe XD.
- Performs testing and quality assurance for all emails through tools like Litmus and Email on Acid.
- Assist with developing and executing email campaigns in an accurate and efficient manner consistent with the client's marketing strategy while still meeting CAN-SPAM requirements.

REVIEWS

"Highly recommend. Scott is extremely knowledgeable, pleasant, easy to reach and communicate with, and goes very much above and beyond. He came strongly recommended and I'm grateful for the connection. I've had plenty of positive web-designer experiences in the past, but Scott just raised the bar significantly. Excellent experience all around." - Cynthia

"It was amazing working with Scott. He helped me make the most beautiful website. He was so speedy in response to my emails and questions and made things really easy to understand. Very professional and talented. Thanks Scott! :)" - Carly

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Xelerate LLC — Talent Acquisition Partner III

November 2021 - Present

- Gather requirements from stakeholders to identify the correct profile for their position.
- Built and manage relationships with 10 external stakeholders generating additional projects with the client.
- Tracked efforts around sourcing, submittals, interviews, offers and hires. Performed an analysis
 on the data to generate reports around time to fill, top sourcing channels, top outreach
 messages and more.
- Present weekly reports to stakeholders showing progress, identify process improvements, opportunities to improve efficiency, and to celebrate successes. Utilized pivot tables to highlight information and created charts to increase comprehension of the data.
- Managed meeting minutes and action items during weekly meetings, ensured team and stakeholders are held accountable to action item deadlines.

Hotfoot Recruiters — Sr. Recruiter

July 2019 - October 2021

- Supported our client W.W. Grainger to fill a high volume of requisitions each month.
- Managed and prioritized multiple requisitions, meeting all hiring deadlines.
- Individually responsible for \$350,000 in hire revenue in 2020, exceeding KPIs for the year.
- Partnered with hiring managers to discuss market trends and strategize new sourcing efforts.
- Utilize multiple sourcing strategies and channels including my network, job boards, job fairs and referrals.

Allegis Global Solutions — Recruitment Sourcing Specialist

June 2017 - June 2019

Sharecare — Health Coach

February 2016 - June 2017

1 Stop Recruiting — *Sr. Medical Recruiter*

February 2016 - June 2017

EDUCATION

Arizona State University

B.S. in Exercise Science